<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>writeup on Miast.io</title>
    <link>https://www.miast.io/tags/writeup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in writeup on Miast.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:51:10 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.miast.io/tags/writeup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>THM - Brooklyn Nine Nine</title>
      <link>https://www.miast.io/write-ups/brooklyn-nine-nine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:51:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.miast.io/write-ups/brooklyn-nine-nine/</guid>
      <description>Room Description Brooklyn Nine Nine
This room is aimed for beginner level hackers but anyone can try to hack this box. There are two main intended ways to root the box.
Writeup Enumeration As usual I start off with a nmap scan with the default scripts and enumerate version tags enabled to get a good baseline understanding of what ports and services are enabled.
nmap -sC -sV -oN nmapScan 10.10.x.x Starting Nmap 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open ECSC File Share</title>
      <link>https://www.miast.io/write-ups/fileshare-writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.miast.io/write-ups/fileshare-writeup/</guid>
      <description>This is a writeup for the OpenECSC2024 challenge File Share. The source code and official writeup can be found at the official OpenECSC Github.
Challenge Description You can now share your files for free thanks to our new disruptive technology! Site: https://fileshare.challs.open.ecsc2024.it
Challenge Analysis Reviewing the source code, there are two main points of interest:
1. support.php if (preg_match(&amp;#39;/^[a-f0-9]{30}$/&amp;#39;, $fileid) === 1) { $url = &amp;#39;http://&amp;#39; . getenv(&amp;#39;HEADLESS_HOST&amp;#39;); $chall_url = &amp;#39;http://&amp;#39; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UofTCTF 2024 - Illusion</title>
      <link>https://www.miast.io/write-ups/illusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 15:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.miast.io/write-ups/illusion/</guid>
      <description>UofTCTF 2024 forensics/Illusion Writeup We&amp;rsquo;re given a PCAP file with a lot of traffic to and from one IP address. Looking into it, it&amp;rsquo;s mainly HTTP traffic, with some calls to a cloned Google.com page, and a GET request for an image. The requests to the images caught my interest, as they don&amp;rsquo;t return any image data, just a 200 OK.
The GUID string looks like base64, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t decode to anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cybergon CTF</title>
      <link>https://www.miast.io/write-ups/cybergon-ctf-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 16:13:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.miast.io/write-ups/cybergon-ctf-2023/</guid>
      <description>Forensics - XIPPER This file is something wrong. Can you open it before the winter season?
In this challenge we are initially given a file called xipper.PNG. Running file on the PNG shows that it is actually a ZIP file. However, when attempting to unzip the file we get the following error:
$ unzip xipper.zip Archive: xipper.zip file #1: bad zipfile offset (local header sig): 0 Opening the file in a hex editor, we see the first 4 bytes are wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
